<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <array name="data_picture_serial">
        <item>@drawable/poster_flash</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_dragon_ball</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_grey_anatomy</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_hanna</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_family_guy</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_fairytail</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_naruto_shipudden</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_shameless</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_the_simpson</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_the_umbrella</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_ncis</item>
    </array>

    <string-array name="data_name_serial">
        <item>The Flash</item>
        <item>Dragon Ball</item>
        <item>Grey\'s Anatomy</item>
        <item>Hanna</item>
        <item>Family Guy</item>
        <item>Fairy Tail</item>
        <item>Naruto Shippūden</item>
        <item>Shameless</item>
        <item>The Simpsons</item>
        <item>The Umbrella Academy</item>
        <item>NCIS</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_name_crew_serial">
        <item>Geoff Johns</item>
        <item>Akira Toriyama</item>
        <item>Shonda Rhimes</item>
        <item>David Farr</item>
        <item>Seth MacFarlane</item>
        <item>Tetsuya Kakihara</item>
        <item>Junko Takeuchi</item>
        <item>Paul Abbott</item>
        <item>Matt Groening</item>
        <item>Steve Blackman</item>
        <item>Don McGill</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="detail_position_serial">
        <item>Creator</item>
        <item>Creator</item>
        <item>Creator</item>
        <item>Creator</item>
        <item>Creator</item>
        <item>Voice</item>
        <item>Voice</item>
        <item>Creator</item>
        <item>Creator</item>
        <item>Creator</item>
        <item>Creator</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="data_description_serial">
        <item>After a particle accelerator causes a freak storm, CSI Investigator Barry Allen is struck by lightning and falls into a coma. Months later he awakens with the power of super speed, granting him the ability to move through Central City like an unseen guardian angel. Though initially excited by his newfound powers, Barry is shocked to discover he is not the only "meta-human" who was created in the wake of the accelerator explosion and not everyone is using their new powers for good. Barry partners with S.T.A.R. Labs and dedicates his life to protect the innocent. For now, only a few close friends and associates know that Barry is literally the fastest man alive, but it won\'t be long before the world learns what Barry Allen has become.</item>
        <item>Long ago in the mountains, a fighting master known as Gohan discovered a strange boy whom he named Goku. Gohan raised him and trained Goku in martial arts until he died. The young and very strong boy was on his own, but easily managed. Then one day, Goku met a teenage girl named Bulma, whose search for the mystical Dragon Balls brought her to Goku\'s home. Together, they set off to find all seven and to grant her wish.</item>
        <item>Follows the personal and professional lives of a group of doctors at Seattle\’s Grey Sloan Memorial Hospital.</item>
        <item>This thriller and coming-of-age drama follows the journey of an extraordinary young girl as she evades the relentless pursuit of an off-book CIA agent and tries to unearth the truth behind who she is. Based on the 2011 Joe Wright film. </item>
        <item>Sick, twisted, politically incorrect and Freakin Sweet animated series featuring the adventures of the dysfunctional Griffin family. Bumbling Peter and long-suffering Lois have three kids. Stewie (a brilliant but sadistic baby bent on killing his mother and taking over the world), Meg (the oldest, and is the most unpopular girl in town) and Chris (the middle kid, he\'s not very bright but has a passion for movies). The final member of the family is Brian - a talking dog and much more than a pet, he keeps Stewie in check whilst sipping Martinis and sorting through his own life issues.</item>
        <item>Lucy is a 17-year-old girl, who wants to be a full-fledged mage. One day when visiting Harujion Town, she meets Natsu, a young man who gets sick easily by any type of transportation. But Natsu isn\'t just any ordinary kid, he\'s a member of one of the world\'s most infamous mage guilds: Fairy Tail.</item>
        <item>Naruto Shippuuden is the continuation of the original animated TV series Naruto.The story revolves around an older and slightly more matured Uzumaki Naruto and his quest to save his friend Uchiha Sasuke from the grips of the snake-like Shinobi, Orochimaru. After 2 and a half years Naruto finally returns to his village of Konoha, and sets about putting his ambitions to work, though it will not be easy, as He has amassed a few (more dangerous) enemies, in the likes of the shinobi organization; Akatsuki.</item>
        <item>Chicagoan Frank Gallagher is the proud single dad of six smart, industrious, independent kids, who without him would be perhaps better off. When Frank\'s not at the bar spending what little money they have, he\'s passed out on the floor. But the kids have found ways to grow up in spite of him. They may not be like any family you know, but they make no apologies for being exactly who they are.</item>
        <item>Set in Springfield, the average American town, the show focuses on the antics and everyday adventures of the Simpson family; Homer, Marge, Bart, Lisa and Maggie, as well as a virtual cast of thousands. Since the beginning, the series has been a pop culture icon, attracting hundreds of celebrities to guest star. The show has also made name for itself in its fearless satirical take on politics, media and American life in general.</item>
        <item>A dysfunctional family of superheroes comes together to solve the mystery of their father\'s death, the threat of the apocalypse and more.</item>
        <item>From murder and espionage to terrorism and stolen submarines, a team of special agents investigates any crime that has a shred of evidence connected to Navy and Marine Corps personnel, regardless of rank or position.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_tgl_serial">
        <item>October 7, 2014</item>
        <item>February 26, 1986</item>
        <item>March 27, 2005</item>
        <item>March 28, 2019</item>
        <item>January 31, 1999</item>
        <item>October 12, 2009</item>
        <item>February 15, 2007</item>
        <item>January 9, 2011</item>
        <item>December 17, 1989</item>
        <item>February 15, 2019</item>
        <item>September 23, 2003</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>